This year, you are very welcome to the YouTube channel,
friends, in today's
video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard and you can see that
200 gram Jain heading is going on in this room but, so
friends, if you want to work in such then this is
a good opportunity to
work here because many
people have already applied here and have
called here, the
quantity number of that idea, I will also tell you here so that from
whichever location we are
talking, if you check the
quantity of the skin and talk about it whether it is
there or not, then I will
tell you the complete details in this video, so
you must watch the recorded video till the end, from this, the
posts of Business Development Executive and Division Development Manager are going on here and this is totally a
pure sales job, so
friends, only if you are interested in the search,
you can apply in this, so due to the increase in the
market, if you have
not subscribed to that channel yet, then subscribe as well.
Also press this bell icon
so that
every upcoming notification reaches you first. So let's
talk
about the second board of directors,
which is a business development act, this is a business
development manager. In this, you have a
sales job, but
I should also tell you whether there is a target or not
because many of my
friends work in this field,
like in the long drive C from ICC,
its process also goes on, they share with
each other's friends, there is a
company titled, in the psychrometric item also,
such a number, only then Anshu works,
these people have set a process for this also,
okay, so here friends, you do
not have any target job like this, yes, there is a
target for this work, but you do
not get so much target here that
you can reduce this zip, so
what will happen to you first in this, so here
if you go on this special day, then
you will have to
ring these people, okay, so
licensing will be done like this,
you will also have to pay attention to
how to activate its license.  It will be done, okay
now you will have to do all this in your job,
apart from this friends, you will have to work on this
health retail product also,
okay,
you will have to maintain this with your health
and especially because there are at
least 10-15 inches inside you, these are the ones for which you
will work and you will have to hire a new APN copy,
okay
I have maintained all this detail here, so you take it
one by one here,
friends, let's talk about how much salary will be given in this
and apart from this, friends, contact
number, okay, let's talk about it,
first of all let's talk about the experience,
here you
can play for two to seven years,
hence the salary here will be given to you from 1 lakh to
spinach etc.,
if you want to call, you can
call on this number of mine,
friend, secondly, here they are
responsible for Reddy, this has also been entered here, so
dry it, whatever you have
in your kitchen  Yes, it is premature, you can send it.
Okay, as soon as you qualify,
you will get a call directly from here. To get
selected in this,
first you will have a phone interview,
after that you may have a video interview, so
please, that's all in this video.
If you liked the video, then like, share and
subscribe. Thank you.